{
  "cards": [
    {
      "_id": "c1",
      "cardFront": "Hund",
      "cardBack": "Dog",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c2",
      "cardFront": "Katze",
      "cardBack": "Cat",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c3",
      "cardFront": "Haus",
      "cardBack": "House",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c4",
      "cardFront": "Auto",
      "cardBack": "Car",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c5",
      "cardFront": "Baum",
      "cardBack": "Tree",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c6",
      "cardFront": "Blume",
      "cardBack": "Flower",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c7",
      "cardFront": "Wasser",
      "cardBack": "Water",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c8",
      "cardFront": "Feuer",
      "cardBack": "Fire",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c9",
      "cardFront": "Erde",
      "cardBack": "Earth",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c10",
      "cardFront": "Luft",
      "cardBack": "Air",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c11",
      "cardFront": "Käse",
      "cardBack": "Cheese",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c12",
      "cardFront": "Vogel",
      "cardBack": "Bird",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c13",
      "cardFront": "Fisch",
      "cardBack": "Fish",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c14",
      "cardFront": "Brot",
      "cardBack": "Bread",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c15",
      "cardFront": "Milch",
      "cardBack": "Milk",
      "deck": "d1",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c16",
      "cardFront": "안녕하세요",
      "cardBack": "Hello",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c17",
      "cardFront": "감사합니다",
      "cardBack": "Thank you",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c18",
      "cardFront": "실례합니다",
      "cardBack": "Excuse me",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c19",
      "cardFront": "네",
      "cardBack": "Yes",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c20",
      "cardFront": "아니요",
      "cardBack": "No",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c21",
      "cardFront": "좋아요",
      "cardBack": "I like it",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c22",
      "cardFront": "미안합니다",
      "cardBack": "I'm sorry",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c23",
      "cardFront": "화장실",
      "cardBack": "Bathroom",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c24",
      "cardFront": "친구",
      "cardBack": "Friend",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c25",
      "cardFront": "가게",
      "cardBack": "Store",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c26",
      "cardFront": "돈",
      "cardBack": "Money",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c27",
      "cardFront": "커피",
      "cardBack": "Coffee",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c28",
      "cardFront": "집",
      "cardBack": "House",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c29",
      "cardFront": "학교",
      "cardBack": "School",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c30",
      "cardFront": "일",
      "cardBack": "Work",
      "deck": "d2",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c31",
      "cardFront": "你好",
      "cardBack": "Hello",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c32",
      "cardFront": "谢谢",
      "cardBack": "Thank you",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c33",
      "cardFront": "请",
      "cardBack": "Please",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c34",
      "cardFront": "对不起",
      "cardBack": "I'm sorry",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c35",
      "cardFront": "再见",
      "cardBack": "Goodbye",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c36",
      "cardFront": "是",
      "cardBack": "Yes",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c37",
      "cardFront": "不是",
      "cardBack": "No",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c38",
      "cardFront": "洗手间",
      "cardBack": "Bathroom",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c39",
      "cardFront": "朋友",
      "cardBack": "Friend",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c40",
      "cardFront": "商店",
      "cardBack": "Store",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c41",
      "cardFront": "钱",
      "cardBack": "Money",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c42",
      "cardFront": "咖啡",
      "cardBack": "Coffee",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c43",
      "cardFront": "家",
      "cardBack": "House",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c44",
      "cardFront": "学校",
      "cardBack": "School",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    },
    {
      "_id": "c45",
      "cardFront": "工作",
      "cardBack": "Work",
      "deck": "d3",
      "user": "u1"
    }
  ],
  "decks": [
    {
      "_id": "d1",
      "demo": true,
      "name": "German",
      "user": "u1",
      "cards": [
        {
          "_id": "c1",
          "cardFront": "Hund",
          "cardBack": "Dog",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c2",
          "cardFront": "Katze",
          "cardBack": "Cat",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c3",
          "cardFront": "Haus",
          "cardBack": "House",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c4",
          "cardFront": "Auto",
          "cardBack": "Car",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c5",
          "cardFront": "Baum",
          "cardBack": "Tree",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c6",
          "cardFront": "Blume",
          "cardBack": "Flower",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c7",
          "cardFront": "Wasser",
          "cardBack": "Water",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c8",
          "cardFront": "Feuer",
          "cardBack": "Fire",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c9",
          "cardFront": "Erde",
          "cardBack": "Earth",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c10",
          "cardFront": "Luft",
          "cardBack": "Air",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c11",
          "cardFront": "Käse",
          "cardBack": "Cheese",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c12",
          "cardFront": "Vogel",
          "cardBack": "Bird",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c13",
          "cardFront": "Fisch",
          "cardBack": "Fish",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c14",
          "cardFront": "Brot",
          "cardBack": "Bread",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c15",
          "cardFront": "Milch",
          "cardBack": "Milk",
          "deck": "d1",
          "user": "u1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "_id": "d2",
      "demo": true,
      "name": "Korean",
      "user": "u1",
      "cards": [
        {
          "_id": "c16",
          "cardFront": "안녕하세요",
          "cardBack": "Hello",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c17",
          "cardFront": "감사합니다",
          "cardBack": "Thank you",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c18",
          "cardFront": "실례합니다",
          "cardBack": "Excuse me",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c19",
          "cardFront": "네",
          "cardBack": "Yes",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c20",
          "cardFront": "아니요",
          "cardBack": "No",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c21",
          "cardFront": "좋아요",
          "cardBack": "I like it",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c22",
          "cardFront": "미안합니다",
          "cardBack": "I'm sorry",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c23",
          "cardFront": "화장실",
          "cardBack": "Bathroom",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c24",
          "cardFront": "친구",
          "cardBack": "Friend",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c25",
          "cardFront": "가게",
          "cardBack": "Store",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c26",
          "cardFront": "돈",
          "cardBack": "Money",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c27",
          "cardFront": "커피",
          "cardBack": "Coffee",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c28",
          "cardFront": "집",
          "cardBack": "House",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c29",
          "cardFront": "학교",
          "cardBack": "School",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c30",
          "cardFront": "일",
          "cardBack": "Work",
          "deck": "d2",
          "user": "u1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "_id": "d3",
      "demo": true,
      "name": "Chinese",
      "user": "u1",
      "cards": [
        {
          "_id": "c31",
          "cardFront": "你好",
          "cardBack": "Hello",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c32",
          "cardFront": "谢谢",
          "cardBack": "Thank you",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c33",
          "cardFront": "请",
          "cardBack": "Please",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c34",
          "cardFront": "对不起",
          "cardBack": "I'm sorry",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c35",
          "cardFront": "再见",
          "cardBack": "Goodbye",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c36",
          "cardFront": "是",
          "cardBack": "Yes",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c37",
          "cardFront": "不是",
          "cardBack": "No",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c38",
          "cardFront": "洗手间",
          "cardBack": "Bathroom",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c39",
          "cardFront": "朋友",
          "cardBack": "Friend",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c40",
          "cardFront": "商店",
          "cardBack": "Store",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c41",
          "cardFront": "钱",
          "cardBack": "Money",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c42",
          "cardFront": "咖啡",
          "cardBack": "Coffee",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c43",
          "cardFront": "家",
          "cardBack": "House",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c44",
          "cardFront": "学校",
          "cardBack": "School",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        },
        {
          "_id": "c45",
          "cardFront": "工作",
          "cardBack": "Work",
          "deck": "d3",
          "user": "u1"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "_id": "u1",
      "username": "demoUser",
      "decks": ["d1", "d2", "d3"]
    }
  ]
}
